wirednewyork.com 2013-12-07

# Privacy Policy | Wired New York

## How we gather information from users

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as discussion board, newsletters, news updates and other products.

Like most Web sites, Wired New York also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your internet service provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customize the site’s features according to your preferences. 

## What we do with the information we collect

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and advertising, and we sometimes permit our advertising and promotional partners to call to your attention products, special offers and unique content we believe might be of interest to you. We offer you the opportunity to elect not to receive direct communications sent by our advertisers or promotional partners, as described below. 

Aggregated information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive). Again, this information does not include any personally identifiable information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually.

We may use personally identifiable information collected on Wired New York to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; our terms of service and privacy policy and other topics we think you might find of interest.

Personally identifiable information collected by Wired New York may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service provider, for example) may access such information. We will use your information only as permitted by law. 

## Affiliated sites, linked sites and advertisements

Wired New York expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a Wired New York page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through Wired New York you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties.

Wired New York is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. Wired New York does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information on message boards, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of Wired New York and this policy.

## How to add, change, or delete personal information

You may add, change or delete personal information on your profile or registration for activities by contacting us via e-mail. Certain information fields are required and cannot be deleted for security purposes or in accordance with various laws. We encourage you to keep us informed about any changes in your membership information and e-mail address.

## Children

Wired New York does not knowingly collect or solicit personally identifiable information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe Wired New York has any information from or about anyone under 13, please contact us.

## How to reach us

You may contact us if you have any questions regarding the content and material on our website or if you have any questions about our privacy policies. Please use [the contact form](http://wirednewyork.com/contact/) or email webmaster[AT]wirednewyork.com

## Changes to this policy

Wired New York reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.
